Cuneiform Tablet Collection
Cuneiform Tablet Collection
- Cuneiform tablets
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 479 (CDLI 359), circa 2100-2000; levy on small livestock intended for offerings (Box 27)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 480 (CDLI 90), circa 2100-2000; inspection of workers [selected] for making millstones (Box 27)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 481 (CDLI 60), circa 2100-2000; receipt for leather and bags (Box 27)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 482 (CDLI 393), circa 2100-2000; tax on date palms (Box 27)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 483 (CDLI 398), circa 2100-2000; delivery of wool (Box 27)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 484 (CDLI 455), circa 2100-2000; barley, beer, and bread (Box 28)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 485 (CDLI 354), circa 2100-2000; delivery of hides (Box 28)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 486 (CDLI 68), circa 2100-2000; soldiers [?] and hirelings [?] for field work (Box 28)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 487 (CDLI 365), circa 2100-2000; barley (Box 28)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 488 (CDLI 392), circa 2100-2000; tax on the date palms of Akasal (Box 29)
  - Cuneiform tablet SUL 489 (CDLI 452), circa 2100-2000; inventory (Box 29)
- Miscellaneous
  - Cylinder seal, depicting two single combat scenes between a anthropomorph figure and a horned lion [?] (Box 29)